RAJA CHOKKAR VEL.Y

PHP Developer

Contact

Address:

No.6 Thirunavukarasar Street, Maraimalai Nagar, Chennai

Phone:

+91 7708447004

Email:

chokkarvelraja@gmail.com

Portfolio:

http://myprofileportfolio.herokuapp.com/

Skill Highlights

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Creative UI design maker

Programming

- PHP,
- MySQL,
- CSS,
- Javascript,
- MySQL,
- WebAPI,
- AJAX,
- JQuery,
- PHP-Framework (Laravel & Shopware),
- JS-Framework (React js & Angular js).

Education

- Completed SSLC with 86.8% in KVS Higher Secondary School, Virudhunagar.
- Completed HSC with 75.66% in KVS Higher Secondary School, Virudhunagar.
- Bachelor of Engineering: Computer Science and Engineering – 2014-2018 (CGPA – 6.7), PSNA CET, Dindigul.

Certifications

Programming Languages: JavaScript, HTML, PHP, CSS, MySQL.

Languages

Tamil and English

Personal Details

Date of Birth: 02-12-1996.

Father's Name: J.Yogavel

Hobby: Love to Meet and speak with people, Travel, Listen to

Music, learning throughout my life

Permanent Address: 1/4725/5, Renganathapuram road, Rosalpatti, Pandian nagar, Virudhunagar, 626001.

Summary

Web Developer specializing in Front end development and Backend development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML, PHP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL, WebAPI, JSON, AJAX, JQuery, PHP-Framework(Laravel, Shopware) and JS-Framework (React js, Angular js). Strong background in project management and customer relations.

Experience

1) Web Developer – July 2018 to November 2019

Magnet Multi Operation Pvt Itd, Chennai

- Cooperate with German customers and providing the best solutions for them.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end, payment option websites and as well as challenging back-end server code.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.
- Websites developed :
 - o https://www.pilotenhemden-shop.de/
 - o https://nordhandel.de/
- 2) Junior Developer December 2019 to December 2020

Auditics Pvt ltd, Chennai

- Developed various websites with the help of Laravel Framework.
- Created web automation to download monthly reports with the help of Python & Selenium (Web drive).
- Created accounts website with excel functionalities (XIRR, IRR, Future valuation and Loss & Profit statement).
- 3) Web Developer May 2021 to Current

Royal Next International Academy, Chennai

- Developed websites And Admin Panel with the help of Laravel Framework.
- Created websites and mobile app using React js.
- Websites developed :
 - https://royalnextacademy.com/ (Laravel)
 - http://shreesaiedu.com/ (Laravel)
 - http://portal.royalnextacademy.com/ (React js)

Declaration

DATF.

Hereby I	declare that	all the above	ementioned	details are	true to	the best	of my k	nowledge.	I will be
honored	and truthful,	if I get an op	portunity to	serve and	work in v	your este	emed or	ganization.	

DATE.	
PLACE:	(Y.RAJA CHOKKAR VEL)